<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- edited with XMLSpy v2013 (http://www.altova.com) by  () -->
<projects>
    <project>
        <title>SHOW ME THE MONEY</title>
        <author>kern</author>
        <target>10000</target>
        <date>03/24/2013</date>
        <duration>30</duration>
        <decription>I went to see the doctor about my hearing loss and he gave me some medicine and told me to take two
            drops a day in my beer.I've been doing it for 5 days now and I still haven't noticed any improvement.
        </decription>
        <rewards>
            <reward>
                <amount>10</amount>
                <decription>Even though we've been married 14 years, I still look at my wife the same as I did on my
                    wedding day---With regret.
                </decription>
            </reward>
            <reward>
                <amount>50</amount>
                <decription>My legs always feel like jelly after sex.It must be all the running beforehand.</decription>
            </reward>
            <reward>
                <amount>100</amount>
                <decription>My son's school is closed today because "the playground is like an ice rink" So we're off to
                    the ice rink this afternoon.
                </decription>
            </reward>
        </rewards>
    </project>
    <project>
        <title>WHY SO SERIOUS</title>
        <author>cysun</author>
        <target>100000</target>
        <date>04/24/2013</date>
        <duration>365</duration>
        <decription>I went up to a homeless man as I came out of a pub last night and said, "What would you say if I
            asked you to come back to my house for a few drinks and a 3 course meal in front of the fireplace?" "I'd say
            yes," he replied. "Exactly," I said, shaking my head and walking away, "What the fuck is wrong with women
            these days?"
        </decription>
        <rewards>
            <reward>
                <amount>1000</amount>
                <decription>We were that poor when I was a child, my bath toys used to be a couple of dirty dishes and
                    some cutlery.
                </decription>
            </reward>
            <reward>
                <amount>5000</amount>
                <decription>As my girlfriend started to whine, I gently patted her back, "That's right. Let it all out."
                    But it doesn't matter how much air you remove, you can never get your blow-up doll back in the box.
                </decription>
            </reward>
            <reward>
                <amount>20000</amount>
                <decription>Whenever my wife says, "We need to talk" I never seem to get much of a chance.</decription>
            </reward>
        </rewards>
    </project>
    <project>
        <title>LEAVE YOUR SLEEP</title>
        <author>cs320stu31</author>
        <target>500</target>
        <date>03/24/2013</date>
        <duration>3</duration>
        <decription>My daughter was asked to draw something from her personal life for a school project. After, she
            showed me and I said, "Darling, where did you see pink elephant and a gorilla standing beside a waterfall?"
            "It's not," she replied. "It's mummy and Uncle Kev in the shower."
        </decription>
        <rewards>
            <reward>
                <amount>1000</amount>
                <decription>I think someone may be sending me death threats. Woke up this morning with a Tesco burger on
                    my pillow.
                </decription>
            </reward>
            <reward>
                <amount>5000</amount>
                <decription>New releases this week at Blockbuster - The staff.</decription>
            </reward>
            <reward>
                <amount>20000</amount>
                <decription>Whenever my wife says, "We need to talk" I never seem to get much of a chance.</decription>
            </reward>
        </rewards>
    </project>
    <project>
        <title>EYE OF SAURON</title>
        <author>kern</author>
        <target>5000</target>
        <date>03/24/2013</date>
        <duration>18</duration>
        <decription>Our neighbour's dog shit in our garden so my mum told me to get a shovel and throw it over the
            fence. I don't see what that solved, now we've got dog shit in our garden and the neighbours have our
            shovel.
        </decription>
        <rewards>
            <reward>
                <amount>10</amount>
                <decription>Tesco are giving treble points on your Clubcard for all burgers and petrol, starting
                    Monday.The deal is called Only Fuel and Horses.
                </decription>
            </reward>
            <reward>
                <amount>20</amount>
                <decription>I can't believe how thick the snow is out there. I asked a snowman for the time and he just
                    stared at me.
                </decription>
            </reward>
            <reward>
                <amount>50</amount>
                <decription>My daughter admitted that she is having lesbian sex with her best friend. As a reward for
                    her honesty, I bought her a video camera.
                </decription>
            </reward>
        </rewards>
    </project>
    <project>
        <title>GREED IS GOOD</title>
        <author>cysun</author>
        <target>9999999</target>
        <date>02/24/2013</date>
        <duration>100</duration>
        <decription>My boss called me into his office today. He said, "I still think you're not too bright at all, Kev.
            But you have come early to work for the past 2 years. You deserve a reward." "Gee, thanks boss!" I said.
            "What's my reward then?" "How does a brand new car sound?" he asked, smiling. I said, "Vrooom, vrooooom."
        </decription>
        <rewards>
            <reward>
                <amount>999</amount>
                <decription>I got sacked tonight for refusing to serve some girl who'd clearly had far too many already.
                    The fat bitch complained to my McManager.
                </decription>
            </reward>
            <reward>
                <amount>9999</amount>
                <decription>If women who sleep around too much were labelled "heroes" instead of "sluts", us guys would
                    be having a lot more sex. Someone fucked up here...
                </decription>
            </reward>
            <reward>
                <amount>99999</amount>
                <decription>I've just seen Black Hawk Down in 3D. It was brilliant. Who needs HMV or Blockbusters when
                    you live in Vauxhall?
                </decription>
            </reward>
        </rewards>
    </project>
</projects>
